(Loading)
(Dungeon Pass)
(Truth Inn)
(The Truth)
=The Truth (Season 4)=
(All persons, backgrounds,
and descriptions are fictional.)
(Settings and actions are setups.)
(All photos and videos)
(are authorized.)
(Safety measures were taken
during shooting. Don't try this at home.)
(Parental supervision required
for underage viewers.)
(Enter game.)
(Previous episode)
Where are we?
Let us out!
Who are you?
Ke Stubborn.
Who?
Are you two putting on a show?
Do you know what year it is?
Year 260.
It's year 2026.
Something's not right.
Do you know what that sound is?
The Ghost Armor.
Who's that?
Isn't that Curator Tui?
Anyone who wears the ghost soldier armor
(The armor makes its wearer bleed)
will bleed and die.
What's this?
There's a skull on it.
An "R".
It must be this organization's logo.
The Touch Today Group.
(The Touch Today Group)
- Don't move!
Boss!
Don't move!
You know the Touch Today Group, right?
I'm
the boss.
I joined an organization.
Who are you?
See the "R" logo?
It's R Corporation.
R Corporation is actually
a notorious
criminal organization.
Are they studying us?
Maybe a certain organ
or body tissue
of the ancient bodies.
To recreate the Longdong Potion.
An alchemy potion.
(R Corporation wants
to recreate the Qide Longdong Potion)
Take another look
at the business license.
There should be something here.
Here's an internal file.
(Internal File, Top Secret)
(R Corporation is a global covert group
researching rebirth)
Top secret.
Global
covert group.
(Secret project)
R Corporation.
Secret project.
Including Qide Longdong Potion.
Top-secret project.
(R Corporation Summary)
(A biotech company on the surface,
a criminal organization underneath)
(To recreate the Qide Longdong Potion
through biological testing)
Wait, there's an org chart.
(Tui City Branch Chief: Curator Tui)
Tui City branch is led by Curator Tui.
(Curator Tui works for R Corporation)
Buy equipment under the Procurement Dept.
Mission, steal, intercept.
Black market.
Buy historical treasures
on the black market.
Conduct bioteh research
under the R&D Dept.
His mission is to use treasures
as test materials
for biological experiments.
The results are used
to develop special drugs.
(R Corporation uses the three
living treasures to make special drugs)
(Name: R Biotech Group)
(Mission: Steal, intercept,
and buy treasures on the black market)
(Use the treasures
for biological testing)
(Apply the results to special drugs)
(R Corporation Summary
Tui City Branch Chief: Curator Tui)
(A biotech company on the surface,
a criminal organization underneath)
(To recreate the Qide Longdong Potion
through biological testing)
Let's keep looking.
There must be more in here.
There's something.
A lot of stuff.
Two ghost soldier armors.
Guys.
I found what you're missing.
What's this?
They took your gallstones.
(Yang Glory's gallstones)
Gallstones.
An appendix.
This is an appendix.
(Ke Stubborn's appendix)
Well, they did remove your gallstone.
That's practically charity.
Free surgery.
(I'd rather not)
(The missing body parts
from the three living treasures)
(Ke Stubborn's appendix)
(Yang Glory's gallstones)
(Ning Waver's left thumb)
They must've taken these
to study your bodies
and see if they can...
Extract the ingredients for the potion.
Exactly.
(R Corporation took parts
of their bodies)
(to study the Qide Longdong Potion)
(Why does Ning Waver
still have his left thumb?)
Top-secret passcode.
Take a guess.
Top secret.
That's a lot of blood.
(A five-digit passcode)
Five digits.
Qide Longdong potion.
(Qide Longdong potion)
It's possible.
Qide Longdong potion.
Right.
Qide
Longdong potion.
Impressive.
Okay.
Wait.
It's a secret passage.
(Hidden space behind the cabinet)
(Found a box)
What's this?
Slide it
in the direction of the arrows.
On both sides.
Come on. Let's check it out.
What's this?
There's a light.
Light? What's the light mean?
What's the light mean?
Ning, I get it now.
It's a projector.
We need to project it onto a surface.
A projector?
(The box can project images)
Yeah.
Here.
I'll do it.
Hang on.
Move your butt. Okay.
I'll take it.
R Corporation Top-Secret Project.
Tui City Operation. Top Secret.
(R Corporation Top Secret
Tui City Operation)
Do you want
to load completed Tui City missions?
Yes!
Yes.
During the Tui, Li, Kuang Era,
rumors of the Longdong Army
and Ghost Soldiers spread.
Steal artifacts
and corpses
for biotech research.
Take over Tui Exhibition Hall.
This is completed.
Completed.
So
they robbed tombs to steal the bodies.
Steal the Tui, Li, Kuang Era bodies
of Ning Waver,
Ke Stubborn,
and Yang Glory.
Three ancient corpses.
Completed.
It's done.
Okay.
Use the Ghost Soldier rumors
to capture villagers
for biological testing.
(R Corporation used the rumors)
There were Ghost Soldier rumors.
(to capture villagers for testing)
It's been uneasy lately.
Many villagers
have gone missing
because of the rumors.
Inject them
with Qide Longdong Potion extracted
from the ancient corpses.
Biotest failed.
All subjects were poisoned
and turned into mummies.
Conclusion, only living samples
work.
Got it.
That means
they had to wake us.
Living treasures.
But they never expected
Curator Tui
to die
before extraction.
So the plan
was never completed.
(Curator Tui died
before the extraction was complete)
That explains it.
The culprit found out
and wanted
to stop R Corporation's plan.
Right.
So he killed Curator Tui.
Exactly.
(Culprit's motive)
(Kill Curator Tui
to stop Tui City Operation)
There's more.
Research shows
the Qide Longdong Potion
is highly effective.
Modern technology
can reactivate it
and extract its core substance,
Qide Longdong Extract,
and develop a reactivation serum.
Completed.
(R Corporation
extracted the Qide Longdong Extract)
(and developed a reactivation serum)
Due to magnetic field limits,
the three must be reactivated
inside Tui Exhibition Hall.
Activation serum injected.
They revived one by one
based on their bodies.
Lifespan extended by 10 days.
(The three treasures woke up
after receiving Qide Longdong Extract)
Curator Tui discovered an outside force
knew the three bodies were hidden here
and that they had value.
At the auction,
he used dead villagers' bodies
to fake the three living treasures
as a distraction
and make money.
It's completed.
The reason they revived us
was to use us
for biological testing
to extract Qide Longdong Potion.
(R Corporation revived the three treasures)
Yes.
(to extract Qide Longdong Extract)
Curator Tui wanted
to make more profit.
So he put our clothes
on
dead villagers
and displayed the photos.
That's the exhibition
from yesterday's auction.
Three sets of clothes.
He claimed they were the three treasures
to make a fortune.
(Curator Tui disguised dead villagers)
(as the three treasures
to make more profit)
Why were you two there?
How did he get out first?
I woke up first.
He woke up first.
You woke up first
and became a security guard?
(Why did Ning Waver wake up first)
(and become a guard
at Tui Exhibition Hall?)
And you escaped by yourself.
And joined us.
Very suspicious.
You adapted so quickly.
You learned so much
in such a short time.
You understood the modern world
and...
Fine, I'll tell you.
Come clean.
This is what happened.
I woke up
inside that cabinet.
After I woke up,
Curator Tui came in.
He was right there,
so I pretended to be asleep.
He searched my body.
I didn't know what he was looking for.
Now I do.
He was probably checking if I was alive.
Then he checked me again.
He said the three bodies
were ready,
but needed time
to wake up.
After he left,
I tried pushing
the glass door.
It opened.
I wanted to save them.
But I couldn't.
(Yang Glory and Ke Stubborn
hadn't awakened yet)
I searched for a way to save them.
Then I found
a book
(Tui Exhibition Hall)
named Tui Exhibition Hall.
It recorded what happened in our era,
but nothing about the years after.
The 2000s, year 2026.
I knew nothing about it.
I was shocked.
Had 2,000 years
passed?
Then I heard someone say
the auction tomorrow
would display the three
living treasures.
The three living treasures.
Could they be us?
So I made my move.
The next day,
I sneaked into the exhibition hall
to save them.
I wanted to save them.
I was already wearing ancient clothes,
so I blended in.
I caught up with them.
They were patrolling.
He introduced himself.
He said his name was Hehe.
I'm Ding Tian.
He said his name was Ding Tian.
Then I thought...
Hehe, Ding Tian.
So I picked two characters too.
I called myself Ning Bo.
That's the whole story.
Yeah, that's my background.
Okay.
Didn't you notice anything
when you were with him?
We only knew him for ten minutes.
(I shouldn't have asked)
Look.
Photo.
Here. What's this?
This is so cool.
(Hehe in ghost soldier armor)
Wait, who is this?
This is He. We can tell.
But who is this?
A friend of mine.
(Photo of Hehe and his friend)
Your friend?
(Why does R Corporation have their photo?)
Fine, I'll explain.
Okay, go ahead.
I'm a completely whole person.
(Who asked?)
Whole?
You have your appendix.
How do you prove you're whole?
You still have your appendix
and gallstones.
I have everything.
I'm perfectly complete.
Who are the two people in the photo?
One is me.
The other is...
His name is Helpful Contact.
(Hehe, Helpful Contact)
(Hehe's friend sent Jin Da)
The one with his back to us
(R Corporation's location)
has a really cool name.
He's called "Heartthrob".
(Heartthrob)
Heartthrob.
He joined an organization
led by Thousand-Faced Eagle King.
You're in that organization too?
Yes, I am.
(Thousand-Faced Eagle King
member update)
(Helpful Contact, Heartthrob,
Jin Da, Hehe)
There's a group chat.
Someone
named Heartthrob
sent me a message.
He said
(Thousand-Faced Eagle King group chat)
we found an organization
named Corrupt Corporation.
They planned
to use Ghost Soldier rumors
to capture innocent villagers
for biological testing.
(Kind Villager: Count me in)
So he asked me
to help stop them.
(Hehe: Sure, I'm in)
How?
(How do we do it?)
We disguised as the ghost soldiers
(Heartthrob: We'll pose as ghost soldiers and infiltrate Corrupt Corporation)
and rescued the villagers.
Well, so...
On May 5,
I joined the organization.
(Timeline: Joined on May 5)
On May 7,
(Rescue mission assigned on May 7)
they gave me the mission.
On May 8,
Heartthrob, Helpful Contact,
(Hehe, Heartthrob, and Helpful Contact)
and I
(rescued the villagers on May 8)
disguised ourselves
as ghost soldiers
to rescue the villagers.
This photo was taken
during the rescue.
(The villagers were rescued
by Thousand-Faced Eagle King)
Find them!
How did they disappear
after we locked them up?
We need to hide first.
Wait.
Aren't we all martial artists?
(Ancient instincts kicking in late)
Why don't we fight them?
What are we afraid of?
(Why are we hiding?)
Right, I forgot who we are.
Exactly.
I'm Ning Waver.
(Swift Footwork)
(Fang Moon Blade)
I'm Fang Moon Blade.
Where did they go?
They're coming.
Find them!
He's coming for us!
What do we do?
In here?
Hide in here?
Over there.
Hide under the bed.
Here.
Where are they?
Get inside.
Quick!
Close the door!
Close it!
How did they disappear
after we locked them up?
Search again.
(Why is Mr. Cui at R Corporation?)
Check over there.
He's coming.
Don't let me catch them.
Or
I'll make them pay.
It's not a big place.
You search there.
We'll split up.
Where are they hiding?
I'll check there.
Nothing here.
(What are you doing?)
(Top Secret)
Check that cabinet over there.
Okay.
(Rolling and crawling)
(Same side?)
Where could they have gone?
No. Nobody's here.
Nobody's here.
No one's here.
What do we do?
Let's move somewhere else.
Keep searching.
Come on! Hurry!
(New bonus scenes)
Can we go out now?
(every Sunday at noon)
It's so stuffy.
Open it. Take a look.
Let me see.
Everyone, stay quiet.
Ask him.
Someone will call us soon.
Ask him, did you leave?
You idiots.
I've already escaped R Corporation.
(Provoking the criminals)
Come catch me, idiots.
Alright, let's go.
Let's get out.
Stop teasing the criminals.
I'm the one you're looking for.
The leader of The Touch Today Group.
Alright, take it slow.
Watch your knees.
(Detective reviews the situation)
They suddenly came after us.
An insider
gave us...
Who was the insider?
He gave us a walkie-talkie.
There are two...
No, three organizations now.
(Three organizations: 1. R Corporation)
One is Thousand-Faced Eagle King.
(2. Thousand-Faced Eagle King)
One is The Touch Today Group.
(3. The Touch Today Group)
It's useless.
(The Touch Today Group leader is here)
He should be
from the Thousand-Faced Eagle King.
(Which organization
did that man belong to?)
Hello.
Speak.
Say it.
He's speaking in his dialect.
Your dialect.
What does it mean?
What did he say?
He said I'm Proudblood,
Ruthless, Mad Dragon.
(Proudblood, Ruthless Duke, Mad Dragon)
(Hehe's codename
in Thousand-Faced Eagle King)
Heartthrob, say something.
That's right. I'm Heartthrob.
You're Proudblood,
Ruthless Duke, Mad Dragon.
Our insider was him.
Right.
(Guess: The insider was Heartthrob)
Heartthrob.
(He is from Thousand-Faced Eagle King)
Be careful.
(He went undercover at R Corporation)
Helpful Contact
who infiltrated R Corporation
was captured last night.
Helpful Contact
who infiltrated R Corporation
has been captured.
He's been captured.
(The Helpful Contact
infiltrating R Corporation was captured)
(Who helped Jin Da before?)
Looks like you still don't understand.
All communication devices
are now controlled by R Corporation.
(R Corporation controlled)
The devices are under their control.
(Helpful Contact's device)
So we used this.
They used Helpful Contact's phone...
Got it. No need to repeat.
... to tell Donasia Ronaswa Ulala
to bring the three treasures
to R Corporation's base.
I understand.
Yes, right.
Yeah.
(The message was sent by R Corporation)
Helpful Contact
(Partner: Helpful Contact)
was captured.
(The mysterious location)
The person who sent you the address
is no longer the same person.
Okay. I got it.
(The Helpful Contact
who lured everyone here was fake)
You all need to be careful.
Everyone, stay alert.
Especially when going
to the storage room
to save...
The storage room.
... the real Helpful Contact.
To save the real Helpful Contact.
(The real Helpful Contact is in the storage room)
The real Helpful Contact.
Okay.
Storage room.
That's the storage room.
Press the button to open it.
There.
Press the button.
Push. Push the door.
(We're pushing the door)
=The Truth (Season 4)=
(Storage room, Lab, Pool)
Helpful contact.
Helpful contact!
Where are you?
We're here to help.
(Ah!)
(The real Helpful Contact)
You scared me.
Come here.
He's locked up.
Who are you guys?
Thousand-Faced Eagle King.
A thousand faces blend in the crowd.
A thousand faces blend in the crowd,
one true...
Wait, let him say the second half.
One true purpose to help mankind.
(Identity confirmed)
Man, we're on the same side.
We're in the same organization.
You don't remember me?
Who are you?
You two saved the villagers together.
Don't you remember?
You came to rescue me, right?
Yes.
Help me then.
(Come save me)
The key. Where's the key?
What key?
We can open it with our bare hands.
We know martial arts.
We can just break the chain.
(Local accent, off the cuff)
Couldn't you do it yourself?
It's already this loose.
Man, you...
Look at this.
Careful.
Helpful Contact.
Okay, Helpful Contact.
Let's sit on the bed first.
So what exactly happened?
Helpful Contact.
Yeah, Helpful Contact.
I went undercover at R Corporation.
But I didn't expect...
their boss found me.
Then...
they brought me here
and tortured me for four hours.
(Helpful Contact was discovered
while undercover at R Corporation)
Before that, I texted a few members
of the Thousand-Faced Eagle King.
I hoped they could find a way
to take the living treasures away
from the auction
and keep them safe.
(Helpful Contact posted a mission)
But because of that,
(to take the living treasure
from the auction)
R Corporation used my identity
to send false information
to one of you
and trick you into coming here.
(R Corporation sent Jin a fake location)
(to lure the three treasures in)
Right.
Curator Tui...
He should have
Thousand-Faced Eagle King's
kite spool.
But after what happened to him today,
R Corporation moved everything
over here.
Let's search again.
(Curator Tui's office)
A kite.
The kite string used
to send messages.
(Tui Exhibition Hall Investigation)
What is this used for?
It records
the true history
of Thousand-Faced Eagle King.
I hope that you all
can clear Thousand-Faced Eagle King's name.
I know why we need to clear his name.
Because the Tui family
claimed the story
of Thousand-Faced Eagle King
belonged to them.
It's the same thing you want to do.
Yeah, right.
Right?
To stop others from pretending
to be Thousand-Faced Eagle King.
Okay, got it.
There's a piece of paper inside.
Tui Exhibition Hall Investigation
Someone came here
and checked in at Tui Exhibition Hall,
taking pictures of the displays.
I think this must connect
with what we're going
to find downstairs.
To see if it's the same.
Right.
Look, he's measuring the arm length.
I think we need
to remeasure the window's
position later.
Use this picture to locate it.
Definitely.
Well, well, you.
Smart.
Your brain works pretty well.
I'm a complete person.
The founder
of Thousand-Faced Eagle King.
Read what's written on it.
These are all names.
Yang Glory.
Yan Reason.
Jin Thrifty.
These are the names
of the villagers from back then.
They're the real Thousand-Faced Eagle King.
And...
There's also a key.
Right, a small key.
There's a lock
in private exhibition room.
This key might be the one
the curator left here.
Right. Should we go check it out?
Alright, everyone. Here's the situation.
I also have some criminal evidence
against R Corporation.
You should've said that earlier.
Once we leave here,
we can report them.
But there's one serious problem.
We can't leave yet.
What is it?
What?
R Corporation
kidnapped innocent villagers
for biological experiments.
Before you leave,
you have to rescue them.
The rescue mission.
(Side Quest) We're descendants
of the Thousand-Faced Eagle King.
(Side Quest Activated)
Right.
(Rescue the captive villagers)
Our ancestors
were true heroes.
Of course.
(Carry on their legacy)
No, I am.
The Thousand-Faced Eagle King
was founded
because of
the Longdong Army.
That's right.
That's my dream.
Peace across the land.
May all live in harmony.
Wait.
A poem just came to mind.
The army unleashed!
Defend our homeland!
(The Longdong spirit lives on!)
Longdong still stands!
(Getting fired up again)
All I know is...
Go ahead.
The villagers are on the second floor.
Okay, got it.
We'll rescue them.
Leave it to us.
(Leave it to Thousand-Faced Eagle King)
I will be the hero.
According to my investigation,
the access card to the room
holding the villagers
is placed
in a safe
that requires a voice command to open.
Okay.
(The voice command box below)
You can find the voice command here.
(stores the access card
to the detention room)
Okay.
(Screen for voice command)
But as far as I know,
the command only works for two minutes.
Okay.
So it's not enough time
to read the command here
then going to open the safe.
Best is you all are split
into two groups.
Three each.
One group stays here
to read the command.
The other group standbys at the safe.
(They need to work in groups
to use the command)
One more important thing.
The group who reads the commands
must find me after you succeed.
I will bring them
to my pre-arranged car
to help the ones downstairs.
(Three of them go with the helpful contact)
The other three saving the villagers
(The other three will save the villagers)
must not make any noise
under any circumstances.
Got it.
Or you will alert R Corporation's
patrolling security.
That's right.
(Bad feeling about this)
A reminder.
Okay.
The three going to save the villagers
need to be quick and agile.
We're doomed. We're disabled.
We're disabled.
(We probably can't go)
We're half-disabled.
We both.
You're just a fence-sitter.
He.
I just realized.
Okay.
They'll stay here for the secret.
How will the people below know?
Through what?
(How will they get the key
to save the villagers?)
Wait. Let's see.
Could it be something like charades?
They'll have to guess the answer.
Outside the window.
Does this open up?
No way.
I don't think so.
It really is.
Let's check this out first.
Here.
We can look here.
This way.
We'll act it out here.
We can't make any noise.
So the three of us will stay.
You guys watch us from down there.
Yeah.
Okay.
Alright. It's decided. Let's go.
The three of us will go.
We'll read the command.
(Assignment: He, Ding, Ke mime the command)
Jin, is that alright?
Sure.
Yang.
I'm scared I'll fail you, Ning.
(Ning, Jin, Yang enter the command for the key)
It's such an important mission.
It's alright.
It's been four seasons.
I have the least Golden Keys.
I'm bad at reasoning.
It's time I become useful.
Or I'll be remove next season.
I lost more than I gained.
I'm leaving.
Let's go, Yang.
You can do it.
I have nothing I'm good at.
Right now, watch me, Iron Tank.
Okay.
(Side Quest:
Rescue the imprisoned villagers)
(1. Obtain voice command
to open the safe)
(2. Obtain the key to the room
holding the villagers)
(3. Save the villagers)
Heaven calls upon us.
(A safe containing the keys
to the room holding the villagers)
(Ning, Jin, and Yang arrived
at the designated place)
This is where your chemistry
with He will be tested.
It depends if he can
do a good job.
(Feeling the stress)
You'll do it outside.
You'll show it to Ning.
Sure.
Yes.
He knows Ning better.
He's here.
(Mimer in position)
(Guesser in position)
Read this to obtain the command.
R Corporation is the best.
R Corporation is the best!
(Voice command: Dripping with jewels)
(Report)
Dripping with jewels.
Four words.
Pig.
(Great)
Second word.
(Strip naked)
Strip?
Strip.
Pig strip.
(Not related to stripping)
(Empty)
(Hair)
Pig, strip, head.
Pig, rub hair.
(Let's move on to the third word)
(Baby)
Baby.
Pig, strip, hug.
(What is pig, strip, hug?)
Last word.
(Air)
Breathing.
(I'm getting mad)
(Angry)
Angry mad.
Mad.
(Bingo)
(Connect them)
Mad.
Dripping with jewels.
(Obtained voice command:
Dripping with jewels)
So easy.
(Easy peasy. Who can stop us?)
(Nobody)
Voice command is dripping with jewels.
Voice command has expired.
No.
Time was up.
It expired.
Again.
(Interception came too quickly)
Let's take another look.
The command expired.
(Command expired.
Generating new command)
(Command expired due to timeout)
Command expired.
It just timed out.
(Obtained new voice command)
Just now...
(Clutching at straws)
Go.
(We must win this time)
(Voice command: Clutching at straws)
Four words.
Dog.
Dog, jump.
Jump.
Clutching at straws.
Clutching at straws!
(That's it)
(Quick)
Clutching at straws.
Clutching at straws!
(Side Quest:
Rescue the imprisoned villagers)
It's open.
It worked.
(1. Obtain voice command
to open the safe)
Key to Ginkgo Valley.
(Obtained key to room holding villagers)
We're going to save them.
Go find the car.
Go down to the first floor.
(See you later)
(Rescue efforts split up)
Did you succeed?
Yes.
Let's go.
(Store room, laboratory, swimming pool)
Drive the car to the first floor
to get them.
(Going to meet them)
(Villagers imprisoned)
Firstly, we don't know
what we'll face inside.
Are you both scared?
A little.
No choice. Let's do it.
You both are scared.
She's alright.
What about you? Are you?
I'm alright too, actually.
If you want to scream,
do it now.
Let it out first.
(Scream in advance)
Shout.
When you scream, make it go down.
(Go up when you sigh, go down when you scream)
Okay.
(Found villagers bound by iron chains)
(Carefully)
The chain.
Wake up.
Open it.
Move your hand.
Hands up.
Raise your hands.
Yes.
(Escape area)
Alright. Let's go.
Come.
Quick.
Go first.
Is this an elevator?
(Discovered escape exit)
Go first.
(Support team arrived)
Get down.
Are they going to come down here?
This can go up and down.
(Exit)
This can move.
Let's see what's downstairs.
Just like this.
They're there. It's fine.
Yes.
It's alright then. Get down slowly.
(Exit)
(Escape rope ladder)
Let it down.
Alright.
Come. Step on it.
(The bottom stabilizes the rope ladder)
(The top lets villagers
evacuate peacefully)
It's alright.
Go down slowly.
Careful.
Don't rush.
Pull it tight.
Alright.
Slowly.
Don't rush.
Leave one by one.
Okay.
Thank you.
Alright.
Careful.
Almost there.
Anymore?
Yes.
Slowly.
Careful.
Step by step.
Slowly.
Don't rush it.
Alrighty.
Okay.
Good.
Is Jin coming?
Yes. Step on it first.
It's alright.
Move your leg back.
You need to look down.
It's fine.
It's not that high.
I can't look.
You need to see the ladder.
If you don't,
you won't know where to step.
Just climb on like any other ladder.
Good.
That's it.
Okay.
Pull the rope.
Tha'ts right.
Yes.
Okay.
Almost there.
It's alright. We're all here.
It's the end.
Okay.
Come on, Ning.
Just jump.
(Easy to talk big from down there)
Oh you.
(Two rungs per step)
Slowly.
Slow down, Ning.
It's scary
from this angle.
He's like a huge spider.
(A ghost spider)
It looks like
Ning will step on my head.
On my face.
Alright.
How is he so long?
(Never found any disadvantages
of being tall)
Everyone's here, right?
Yes.
Get in the car.
Four first.
Quick.
Get in.
Leave now.
Hurry.
(Successfully rescued the villagers)
No need to thank us.
If you wish to commend us,
address it to...
Thousand-Faced Eagle King.
That's right.
Goodbye.
Okay.
Bye.
Stay safe.
Goodbye.
Stop!
Don't move!
None of you are getting away.
(R Corporation has caught up)
Fall back!
Don't move!
He's coming with a gun!
Freeze Card.
We're out of Freeze Cards.
(How will they respond now?)
We're really out of cards?
Stop!
Don't move!
(The enemy is closing in)
It's alright.
There are guns and shields.
Hurry!
(Quickly looting the supply drop)
Guns and shields.
Say it sooner.
There are guns too.
Use knockout drops.
Knock them unconscious.
Let's do this, everyone.
Here.
Shield.
You should've told us sooner.
Protect yourselves.
My sword shield!
(Equipped)
Quick!
No one's escaping!
(Hit the enemy in the face to daze them)
Let's work together.
Dual pistols.
Cover me.
We finally found you!
(The enemy has arrived)
Move in!
How am I supposed to cover?
Daze them!
You amateurs!
Amateurs!
Daze them!
Take this!
(All enemies eliminated)
Amateurs!
Behind you!
Behind you, guys!
No wonder my back felt so warm.
Daze them!
You've been dazed now, amateurs!
(All enemies have been dazed)
You alright?
Daze them!
(He's addicted to saying it)
That's not enough.
(Still making sure they're down)
Alright.
We managed to fight them off.
Good.
It's safe now.
Alright.
Everyone,
your vehicle is outside.
Come with me, quickly.
Alright.
Let's go.
Go.
Amateurs!
(Side Quest:
Rescue the Captive Villagers)
([1] Obtain the dynamic
passcode to unlock the safe)
([2] Retrieve the key
to the villagers' holding room)
([3] Rescue the villagers)
What's this?
Even the trash bin is locked?
(Locked Trash Bin)
Let's head back
to the exhibition hall, everyone.
Alright.
Let's go.
Go.
(Returning to the exhibition hall)
The locked-room murder, everyone.
If we can find a concealed passage,
everything will make sense.
That would explain
how the killer entered
this place in advance.
(How was the locked-room
murder carried out?)
(Investigating the Tui Exhibition Hall)
(Checking in at the Tui Exhibition Hall)
(Outside the exhibition hall,
Inside the exhibition hall)
The window positions don't match.
The window outside
doesn't line up
with the sealed window inside.
(There's something wrong
with the window positions)
This photo makes it obvious.
Using the female visitor's
arm length as a reference,
you can tell the two windows
are actually misaligned.
(Inside the exhibition hall)
(Window 1, Window 2)
(Outside the exhibition hall)
(Outside, Inside, Window 1, Window 2)
The sealed window inside
doesn't fit
the open window.
Right.
Which means
someone created
a fake sealed window here.
(Theory: One of the exhibition
hall's windows is fake)
It should be the one near the door.
(Checking in at the Tui Exhibition Hall)
Here's the thing, everyone.
This
photo
on the left,
see it?
That means there should be empty space
behind this display cabinet.
(Exterior photo, Interior photo)
(Theorized corresponding window)
It's not empty.
(This location doesn't correspond
to the corridor window)
(Exterior photo, Interior photo,
Theorized corresponding window)
The window outside can be opened,
but this one is sealed shut.
So what you're saying is,
it's inside this cabinet?
Both sides are possible, right?
(Corresponds to the exterior window)
Maybe it fits that window,
but this one doesn't.
Do you get it?
(Doesn't correspond
to the exterior window)
(He's theory)
(If the window on the right
corresponds to the exterior window,)
(then the left window
matches this cabinet)
I get it.
Let me take a look.
That window might be here.
This window is the one
that's out of place.
Ning, say something.
It's here.
Stand facing that window
and knock on it.
(Knock)
It's here.
Right?
Right.
Is this a window?
Yes, it is.
Alright, this is a window.
Now the next one.
This one.
This one lines up.
This window is correct.
Only this window doesn't match.
Come in. I got it.
(Corresponding windows,
Interior photo, Exterior photo)
(Match confirmed)
There's a window
behind this display cabinet.
(The cabinet corresponds
to the exterior window)
I understand now. The priority
is to move this display cabinet.
Can it be moved?
It opens.
No. That's not it.
(The display cabinet cannot be moved)
Try it from outside.
Here.
(Outside the exhibition hall,
Inside the exhibition hall)
Is there a switch? A latch?
A lock?
Can this be moved?
Wait.
It can.
This works.
Come on. It's like a building block.
Yes.
It's from here.
That explains
the locked-room murder.
The surveillance camera
covers that doorway.
It's out of view.
The killer could crawl
through here and murder him.
(Crime Reconstruction Surveillance
footage auto-syncs every 2 hours)
(Curator entered the exhibition
hall wearing Ghost Armor)
(Killer entered through the window
and murdered the Curator)
(Killer escaped through the window)
Smart.
(Better patch that theory up)
Why was he dressed like
that when he came here at 10:55?
That's the first question.
Right.
But how was he killed?
(Key Question: Why did the Curator
wear Ghost Armor at 10:55?)
(How did the killer murder him?)
Let's check the records,
the check-in logs and the timestamps.
Yanzhi.
May 29, 10:55.
Let's review the footage.
(Cloud sync every 2 hours)
We arrived at 10:00. Right.
(Timeline: 10:00, Ning, Ding,
and He enter the hall for patrol)
We came in at 10:00
and left ten minutes later.
(10:10, Ning, Ding,
and He finish their patrol)
(10:55, Yanzhi clocks in)
The Curator entered at 11:00.
(11:00, A person wearing
the Ghost Armor enters)
Right.
The person wearing the armor
wasn't the Curator.
(Ning's Theory: The person
in Ghost Armor wasn't the Curator.)
Why?
The Curator may have entered
through this passage himself.
He intended to kill someone.
(Ning's theory)
So he hid here in advance,
(The Curator used the window
to avoid cameras)
waiting for the other person.
(The Curator entered the exhibition
hall intending to kill someone)
That other person was the one
wearing the armor,
who entered at 11:00.
During the struggle,
the killer killed the Curator instead.
(The Curator was killed
by the murderer during their struggle)
There's another possibility.
The Curator had arranged
to meet this person
to exchange something.
I thought it was Curator Tui.
I had arranged
to meet him here today.
He told me he had another
appointment at 10:40.
But now,
that person is gone.
What time was your appointment?
10:40.
He was supposed
to meet someone at 10:40.
(Ding Tian's theory: Curator arranged
to meet the killer in the hall.
The Curator told him,
"Come in through here".
(Curator Tui directed
the killer to use the window)
He knew the layout.
Right.
The Curator intended to kill him.
(Curator intended to kill the murderer)
The Curator entered first,
left the blood trail,
then waited here to kill him.
(The Curator entered openly
and left fake blood behind)
But instead, he was killed.
(The Curator attempted to kill
the murderer but was killed instead)
(At 11:00, the victim, Curator Tui,
entered to commit murder.)
We have a key.
It should unlock
this display cabinet.
Knockout drops.
There's a phone here, everyone.
It's a talk between Curator
Tui and his assistant.
It's the Curator Tui's phone.
The first message
was sent on May 27, 2026,
at 3:58PM.
The Curator Tui said,
someone has been inside my office.
The encrypted hard drive
containing R Corporation's
plans is missing.
Fortunately, it will still take several
days to crack the encryption.
Find out who took it
as soon as possible.
The assistant replied, understood.
Then a day later,
at around 3:00 PM,
the assistant sent,
boss, are you available?
I've found out who it is.
Let's discuss it over the phone".
They communicate via calls.
They spoke for one minute.
Then, at 9:00AM. on May 29,
the Curator Tui asked,
where is the exhibition
hall's largest garbage cart?
The assistant replied,
it's usually parked
outside the door
opposite the Ghost Armor.
The assistant then sent the location.
That's the trash bin we saw
when we first came in.
(Why did he ask for cart's location?)
What's this?
Even the trash bin is locked?
Then Wang from AAA Building Materials
also sent a message
at 4:00PM on the 27th.
Wang, make me another steel panel,
identical to the one used
to seal the exhibition hall window.
It's urgent.
You need another one?
I have it in stock. I'll have someone
deliver it immediately.
Perfect.
Which means...
He had this built...
He created the locked-room setup.
(Theory: Curator Tui created
a locked-room crime scene)
Because sealing off the exhibition hall
was also done under his orders.
Right here. Right?
(Effective immediately: The hall
will undergo a full security upgrade)
He
was planning to do something.
Planning something.
Then the third contact,
Black Market Hei.
At 3:00PM on May 28, he messaged, Hei,
I need a bottle of fake blood.
Deliver it to my office.
(Delivery of fake blood in advance)
Upload the Ghost Armor sound effects
(Delivered to Curator Tui's office)
to the exhibition hall's
scheduled broadcast system.
I'll need them.
Hei replied, understood.
Then, at 8:00PM on May 28,
Hei said, Curator Tui,
I've left everything
on your office desk.
Contact me anytime
if you need anything else.
Curator Tui replied,
perfect. I've transferred the payment.
Curator had actually prepared
(Organizing the investigation)
the mechanisms for the crime scene.
Yes.
(Curator prepared
the mechanisms for the crime scene)
He also staged the blood evidence.
(He arranged the blood at the scene)
He also altered the window.
(He modified the window)
Right.
But why would he do all this?
Someone has been inside my office.
The encrypted hard drive
containing R
Corporation's plans is missing.
He intended to kill someone.
Right.
(Curator Tui turned
the exhibition hall into a locked-room)
The person who posed a threat to him.
(He intended to kill someone)
But that person
used
knockout drops.
(Knockout drops)
You know what this is, right?
Let me explain.
This is one of our iconic props.
Really?
Yes.
(Allow us to introduce Tui City's
signature product: Knockout drops)
(Tui Lemen, Fragrance Edition)
Knockout drops, a fragrance
that leaves anyone unconscious.
(Tui Cyber AI Doll, Cyber Edition)
Cyber knokout drops.
(Tui Sweet Foods Factory,
Insomnia Edition)
Extra-strength sleep spray.
That's knockout spray.
(An Glass Factory, Vintage Edition)
Knockout spray.
(Starlight Cafe, Classic Spray Edition)
You can even buy it at the supermarket.
That's Tui City's reality.
Spray them!
(R Corporation × Thousand-Faced
Eagle King Special Edition)
One spray, and you'll pass
out immediately.
Show her.
She'll lose consciousness.
Okay.
Let's check the trash bin outside first.
Let's go.
(General Waste)
What's underneath?
Awakening Pills.
After taking one,
all sedatives become ineffective
for one hour.
(Counters knoukout spray)
So the two of them
were both in that enclosed
(The investigators get excited)
space.
It must have belonged to the Curator.
Right.
The Curator intended to use it
on someone before killing them.
But that person
anticipated his plan.
(Theory: Curator Tui prepared it
in advance to incapacitate the killer)
In fact, all
(The killer learned of the plan
in advance and prepared Awakening Pills)
had been prepared
by him.
Then could the key
have been on Curator Tui?
Down there.
(Turns out he's just good
at searching the floor)
Let's unlock it.
Is there anything scary inside?
(Instantly takes it back)
(Let the fearless one handle it)
I'm going to prove myself.
There's paper inside.
Pour it out.
Like this.
No.
Why?
(Fragment +1)
(Fragment +2)
Long arms.
Nicely done.
Wow.
Your arms must be over a meter long.
(The final fragment)
There we go.
(Hold on)
Let's see what it is. Piece it together.
This looks difficult.
It won't be easy, will it?
It's hard.
I can't understand.
Then let's just use a Restore Card.
(I need to prove myself too)
Seriously, I think we should restore it.
This is far too difficult.
Let me try.
I have a feeling I can do it.
Come on!
(Still determined
to assemble it by hand)
There it is! Alright, it's done!
(He actually put it together!)
You really solved it!
My goodness.
Wow, that's incredible.
You actually managed
to piece it together.
Unbelievable.
(A human-shaped Restore Card)
The person in green first
incapacitated the victim else
where using knockout.
Right.
Then transported the body
through the window.
After that, they entered the exhibition
hall and put the armor on the victim.
Right.
Before leaving,
the person in green dressed
the corpse in the armor.
then escaped through the secret passage,
sealed the passage,
locked it,
and reattached the window frame.
Once that was done,
the locked-room setup was complete.
So this must have been the Curator's
original plan, right?
Yes. That was the Curator's plan.
(Curator Tui's assassination plan)
But the killer discovered it.
Exactly.
The killer used his plan against him.
They knew to use knockout spray first.
so they took
an Awakening Pill beforehand.
Right.
(Ning's theory: The learned of Curator
Tui's assassination plan in advance)
(The killer took an Awakening Pill
beforehand and killed Curator Tui)
Then it's simple.
Who was the Curator meeting
at 10:40?
Who was it?
The person he arranged
to meet was the killer.
Yes.
(The person Curator Tui met
at 10:40 was the murderer)
I've identified the killer.
The only person who could carry
someone through that window
is...
Exactly.
Only her.
That's right.
No, you could do it too.
(Me? How?)
A body can be folded up.
(Fair point)
What's wrong?
What's the matter?
(What's going on?)
Do you know
(Perfect timing)
who the Curator was meeting at 10:40?
I'm not sure.
But today,
someone did send me a private message.
What did it say?
They told me
that between 10:40 and 11:00,
I was to come here
and photograph the Curator
wearing the Ghost Armor
from the front.
(Someone instructed Yanzhi to photograph
the Curator in the Ghost Armor at 10:55)
Who sent you the message?
A member of our corporation.
But I don't know who they are.
(A member
of the Thousand-Faced Eagle King)
(Instructed Yanzhi to photograph
Curator Tui wearing the Ghost Armor)
(Yanzhi was also an undercover member
inside the Tui Exhibition Hall)
Can we see the chat history?
What does it say?
My application has been approved.
I hope you'll become
my partner in this mission.
I look forward to your reply.
Sent at 11:00PM.
on May 28.
It says, Thousand-Faced
Eagle King Mini Program,
Application Status.
They're really well organized.
What's this?
(Let me see)
Step one. Dear Administrator,
I am currently secretly investigating
the conspiracy behind Curator Tui.
I have a mission
that requires assistance from members of the group.
(I want to see it too)
The task...
I'm sorry.
You only need
to photograph Curator Tui
wearing the armor.
Please approve.
And then...
To participate, reply...
This was Yanzhi, right?
Then another group member replied,
on the morning of May 29,
between 10:40 and 11:00,
you are to go to Curator
Tui's private exhibition hall.
Wait at a designated
location inside the exhibition hall,
take a front-facing photograph
of him wearing the armor,
and leave the photograph
inside the exhibition hall
in a natural manner.
The exact location will be sent
to you later.
But everyone,
the more I thought about it,
the more something felt wrong.
So I contacted the five core
members to verify the mission.
They all told me
they had never approved it.
It was fabricated.
Yes. That screenshot was forged.
(An infiltrator
forged a mission announcement)
I just found a phone
inside the exhibition hall.
It should belong to one of you.
Let me see.
Take a look.
We all should.
The phone's unlocked.
Let me check WeChat.
Why does it require Face ID?
Why is this phone locked
down at every level?
Even opening the app
requires Face ID verification.
I'll use your face.
Don't.
It's open.
How did you lock an app like this?
You're asking how to set up Face ID?
Right.
You just press and hold the app,
then the Face ID
option will appear.
It helps protect your privacy.
I learned something new today.
Exactly.
Curator Tui sent this person a message
at 10:00 on May 28,
how did you clean the place?
The staff area is filthy.
Go clean it immediately.
Ning Bo replied, understood, Boss.
Ning Bo.
You...
Are you really from ancient times?
The dragon stirs upon the plains.
(Passes it off with a cute excuse)
There's also a social media post.
Ning Bo wrote, I spent half
an hour watching short videos
without laughing once.
Then I checked my bank account balance
and finally laughed.
(Wow)
So you've been awake all along.
No.
You were never dead.
Then...
(Who is Ning Bo, really?)
The truth is...
I'm from the modern era.
I'm actually
Ning Waver.
And I'm also a member
of the Thousand-Faced Eagle King.
(Ning Bo, Public Identity: Security
Guard at the Tui Exhibition Hall)
(Affiliation: Thousand-Faced Eagle King)
You're a member
of the Thousand-Faced Eagle King?
That's right.
The one with the username,
Introverted Tall Guy.
(Thousand-Faced Eagle King group member)
That's me.
One day,
I discovered the Thousand-Faced
Eagle King's mini program,
so I joined it.
Just like all of you,
I quietly carried out good
deeds behind the scenes.
Then one day, I received a mission,
obtain the three living treasure
at the auction
on the day of the incident.
(Ning Bo receives a mission
from the Thousand-Faced Eagle King)
(Retrieve the three living treasure)
But my true duty
is to serve
as a tomb keeper.
(Another hidden identity)
For generations,
my family has guarded six tombs.
Which six?
The tombs
of the six legendary
heroes we all revere.
(Ning Waver, Jin Thrifty, Ke Stubborn)
(Ding Pillar, Yang Glory, and He Ha)
But one day,
when I went to pay my respects
and burn incense at the cemetery,
I discovered that three
of the graves had been dug up.
(Ke Stubborn)
Ke Stubborn,
(Yang Glory)
Yang Glory,
(Ning Waver)
and my own ancestor's
grave.
The three bodies had disappeared.
So I set out to find them.
While searching the disturbed soil,
I found
a fountain pen shaped like an arrow.
I searched online
to find out where it came from.
The internet told me it was exclusive
to the Tui Exhibition Hall
and used only by VIP guests.
That clue led me here
to apply for a job
at the exhibition hall.
I originally applied to be a cleaner.
But on the day of the auction,
everyone in the exhibition hall
was required to wear period costumes.
So I blended in
with the security guards.
That's why
you saw the boss telling me,
why haven't you cleaned yet?
Go clean that area.
I replied, understood.
But I was searching everywhere.
I had to find those three bodies.
Eventually, I discovered a hidden room,
the same room where the two
of them were rescued.
Then I heard voices inside.
I secretly recorded them.
Listen.
The test results have been confirmed.
These bodies can all be reactivated.
Once we extract the hormones
from their bodies,
we'll be able
to mass-produce superhumans.
(Ning Bo discovered the Qide
Longdong extraction plan beforehand)
Tui City's legendary heroes.
will soon become the sharpest weapons
in our hands.
At that moment, I was terrified.
So I ran.
After a while,
I came back.
Then I saw Ning Waver,
my ancestor,
walking around the exhibition
hall alone.
I was stunned.
I rushed over
and knocked him unconscious
with an elbow strike.
Really?
If he wandered around like this,
Curator Tui would drag him away.
And then,
I tossed him over my shoulder
and carried him home.
Everything he told me
is everything I relayed to you guys
back when we first met.
My ancestor, Ning Waver,
is already at my place.
So my purpose in coming here
this time is to save him
and her.
Understood.
Yes.
(Ning Bo claimed)
Yan Zhi's phone
(to be Ning Waver to protect him)
has this.
Tui Exhibition Hall
face recognition app.
Right?
10:30.
They're probably
the ones entering the auction hall.
Yeah.
Yes.
So they aren't staff members.
Hold on. Who is this ?
(The only person who entered
the exhibition hall before Curator Tui)
Mr. Cui.
He's also one
of Thousand-Faced Eagle King's men?
Yeah.
Why didn't you say so earlier?
I thought I just did?
No, you didn't.
Didn't I?
You didn't.
(Thousand-Faced Eagle King
member update)
(Helpful Contact, Jin Da,
He, Heartthrob,)
(Ning Bo, Yan Zhi, Mr. Cui)
Let's start the interrogation.
We should get ready
to question Mr. Cui.
Alright.
Okay.
(Mr. Cui entered the exhibition hall
before Curator Tui)
(Is he the killer who murdered Mr. Tui?)
(Group Interrogation:
10-minute time limit)
(Group Interrogation,
Goal: Detectives initiate a trial)
(Conduct a 10-minute interrogation
on a specific suspect or NPC)
(to advance the investigation.)
Hand over the phone.
(Nope!)
Bring one over here.
(All confiscated)
Trying to hide key evidence?
Pretending to be from the ancient times.
With your anger control,
you must be
the "killer".
(Usually very calm and collected)
Bring the suspect up.
(Let's start the trial!)
Mr. Cui.
(Bridging the time gap:
Using modern communication tools)
Get over here.
(Instantly teleports)
Someone called for me?
You saved us today,
didn't you?
Come on, sit down.
We're just here to thank you.
(First, get him to drop his guard)
This feels like an interrogation.
(Nervous, tense)
No way.
We're all good friends here.
As per usual,
let's frisk him first.
What are you doing?
Hey, don't.
Why are you getting
all handsy out of nowhere?
That's not cool.
We're just
doing the routine procedure.
(Routine procedure: Frisking)
Just a quick frisk.
Just a quick one.
A quick frisk.
A quick one.
I'm clean.
Totally clean.
There's a piece of paper.
This is a pickup receipt.
Yes.
(Pickup receipt)
The recipient is Boning.
(Recipient: Boning)
Boning?
Isn't it Ning Bo?
Who's Boning?
Boning.
It's you...
Oh, you know me?
Yes.
Actually,
my real name isn't Mr. Cui.
I have a birth name.
I'm Cui Boning.
(Mr. Cui's real name is Cui Boning)
I'm a descendant of Longdong veterans.
(Descendant of Longdong veterans)
Because I really
admire our young marshal back then,
Ning Waver.
That's why I named myself Cui Boning.
(He's a fan)
The anthem I made for him goes like,
(Ning Waver, Boning)
Boning, Boning, Boning, that's me.
Boning, Boning, never forget.
(Ning Bo)
Ning Bo, Ning Bo, Ning Bo, that's you.
Ning Bo, Ning Bo, respect.
(Longdong spirit lives on forever)
Classy.
The item he picked up was a forged card.
(Pickup receipt)
Payment method was cash.
Notes.
Mr. Boning,
the card you requested
to forge takes a few days
due to its complex craftsmanship.
Please use this receipt
to pick it up on June 1st.
What forged card?
Well, it's because there were
some personal matters
between me and Curator Tui.
I originally came here
to investigate him.
But, you see,
his office door
requires a work ID to get in.
(Need a work ID to enter the office)
I don't have one.
Since I don't work here,
I had to get a fake one made.
The card isn't ready yet,
so I have that receipt on me.
I haven't gone to pick it up yet.
So you haven't gotten this card yet.
Yes.
(Cui Boning hasn't
picked up the forged work ID)
This is just the receipt.
Yeah.
I've never stepped foot in his office.
What's that supposed to mean?
Are you hinting that I haven't
searched you thoroughly enough?
Again?
Don't.
Got it.
Take off this blazer, please.
(The detective keeps searching)
All of a sudden?
Take it off.
I really don't have anything.
If you can't find the card,
you gotta prove my innocence.
There really is no card.
Of course.
Is there anything else then?
Let me check.
I'm totally clean.
(Some personal belongings)
(Totally clean)
Do you guys
understand this hand gesture?
Thousand-Faced Eagle King.
(Thousand-Faced Eagle King secret sign)
So you guys know.
We're all from the same organization.
Yes.
Thousand-Faced Eagle King
only has two missions in Tui City.
First,
(Main missions)
protect those three living treasures.
Second,
investigate R Group
and gather enough evidence
of their crimes.
Because I'm basically
an undercover spy.
(Mr. Cui is a spy in R Group)
What's my grudge against Curator Tui?
He dragged away all the folks
from our village
to do some really shady stuff.
So in order to investigate him,
I posed as someone from R Group
to infiltrate this place.
But I haven't
found any useful info yet.
Which is why
I showed up at the auction.
(Mr. Cui tried appeared at the auction)
I figured there'd be
(to investigate Curator Tui)
some clues I needed there.
And then we ran into each other there.
Gotcha.
That's why I was helping you guys.
So going to that auction
was your own call,
not a mission assigned by someone else,
right?
Of course not.
My handle
in Thousand-Faced Eagle King is
Heartthrob Who Loves Meal Kits.
So you two
played those ghost soldiers together.
Yeah.
Rescued his villagers
back in the village.
(He, Helpful Contact, Cui Boning)
Yeah, we also had Helpful Contact with us.
We infiltrated together,
so I could coordinate
with Mad Dragon from the inside.
Yeah.
What's your ID, then?
Mine is Proud something Mad Dragon.
It's
Proudblood, Ruthless Duke, Mad Dragon.
And yours is Leggy something Hunk.
Innocent, Leggy Hunk.
(Shy)
Leggy McShy, Kinda Awkward, Innocent Hunk.
(Group Members)
(He, Jin Da, Cui Boning, Ning Bo)
So you guys are colleagues?
All working for the same team,
pretty much.
I'm honestly just slacking off in there.
Because I've never
gotten a single mission.
I'm just the type
who replies with "Got it"
(Loves to joke around)
to everything.
Today is the 30th.
So your card
won't be ready
until the day after tomorrow.
Yes.
Which means
between May 27th
and May 30th,
you haven't seen Curator Tui at all.
Nope, haven't seen him once.
(Mr. Cui hasn't seen Curator Tui)
I just infiltrated R Group.
So, guys,
does that mean we can
rule him out as a suspect?
Definitely.
(Suspect list)
My name is cleared.
(Mr. Cui is cleared of suspicion)
Yep.
Alright, I'll take my leave.
Alright, thanks.
Thanks for saving our lives.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Thank you for saving us.
I have a question.
Did all of us receive a mission
from Thousand-Faced Eagle King today?
Yeah, I did.
How about you?
Yes.
I got a mission in the group chat.
They wanted me
to show up at the venue
on the day of the auction
and figure out a way to get my hands
on the three living treasures.
I got that same mission too.
You got that too?
Same here.
(Thousand-Faced Eagle King
member mission:)
(Get the three living treasures
at the auction)
What about you?
I'm not part of your organization.
He belongs
to another third-party faction,
The Touch Today Group.
My goal is to steal you
three living treasures
back to my place.
(Thousand-Faced Eagle King:
Get the three living treasures)
(The Touch Today Group: Take the three
living treasures home to protect them)
(R Group: Replicate the Qide Longdong potion
using the three living treasures)
Okay.
Alright.
Got it.
Now we have a angle to work with.
Guys,
what are your respective roles
here?
I...
(Strategy 1: Based on their role
and motive for joining.)
(He's Role: Temp Security Guard)
am a temp security guard,
(Org: Thousand-Faced Eagle King)
working for Thousand-Faced Eagle King.
My mission today
(Mission: Get the three treasures)
is to acquire the finale treasures.
And about my previous mission,
why did I want to scare Curator Tui?
It's because he took my family heirloom,
(Purpose: Retrieve family heirloom)
so I wanted to get my heirloom back.
I'm the treasure restorer here.
(Jin Da's Role: Treasure Restorer)
(Org: Thousand-Faced Eagle King)
I'm also with Thousand-Faced Eagle King.
(Mission: Get the three treasures)
And I knew that Curator Tui
(Purpose: Expose Curator Tui's true colors)
has been posing
as a descendant
of Thousand-Faced Eagle King,
so I didn't want him
getting away with it.
I needed to gather evidence here
and expose this secret to the public.
And what does Ding do?
(Ding Tian's Role: Temp Security Guard)
Security guard.
(Org: The Touch Today Group)
Temporary?
Yeah.
I want to steal
those three family heirlooms
back to my place.
(Purpose: Take and protect
the three living treasures)
I want to protect them.
I used to be a cleaner,
but today I'm a temp security guard.
(Ning Bo's Role:
Cleaner disguised as security guard)
You're with our organization.
(Org: Thousand-Faced Eagle King)
Yeah, I'm with Thousand-Faced Eagle King.
(Mission: Rescue the three treasures)
And my goal is to save
(Purpose: Rescue the two living treasures)
the two living treasures.
Because I know I've already
saved one of them.
(Ning Bo, Jin Da, He, Ding Tian)
(Motives of all four
are not strong enough to kill)
So let's think about this again.
We just need to focus
on what we were doing at 10:40
(10:40 Curator Tui met the killer)
and check what our timelines
look like around then.
Alright?
(Deduction 2: Timeline
Did anyone meet the curator at 10:40?)
Here's my timeline.
I wanted
to attend the exhibition that day.
But I was a cleaner,
and on the day of the exhibition,
(Cleaners were banned from the hall)
cleaners weren't allowed in.
So I disguised myself as a guard.
That's how I got inside.
I was looking around
when someone suddenly came up to me.
Hey, are you the new guard?
I said yes.
It's already ten.
What are you doing?
Hurry and join the patrol.
That worked out, so I joined them.
So I know
one definite time.
We started patrolling at ten.
(They started patrolling at 10:00)
My second question is...
Let me ask you.
After ten o'clock,
the three of us patrolled together.
What did you do ten minutes later?
(He's timeline:)
I found an empty spot.
(10:10-? Rested alone)
I rested alone
while awaiting a message
from the company.
Nothing else.
Okay.
What about you?
(Ding Tian's timeline: 10:10-?)
I was checking the escape route.
I needed to know how to escape
after I pulled it off.
Okay.
I also found somewhere hidden
(Ning's timeline: 10:10-? Waited alone)
and waited for my chance
(To rescue Yang Glory and Ke Stubborn)
to rescue those two.
What about you?
I was repairing the treasure.
(Jin Da's timeline: 10:10-?)
The whole time?
I started at ten.
(Timeline summary)
(Curator Tui arranged
to meet someone at 10:40)
(Entered the exhibition hall at 11:00
wearing ghost soldier armor)
(Found dead at 12:10)
Then everyone had time
to commit the crime.
(All four had time
to commit the crime)
Let's think again.
What conditions did the killer meet?
(Conditions the killer had to meet)
The curator's encrypted hard drive
was missing.
So this person must have
taken the curator's
encrypted hard drive.
Then the curator found out who it was
and decided to kill that person.
That person found out
(Discovered the curator's plan)
and made a plan to kill him first.
(Killed the curator instead)
Exactly.
The chat logs already said
that someone entered his room
and took his encrypted hard drive.
Then he had someone investigate
and found out who it was.
It could've been you.
It could've been me.
Okay.
Curator Tui said
he wanted this man dead.
So he started making plans
and preparing everything.
(Curator Tui's plan: Installing the window)
Then he began planning everything.
(Ghost Armor's voice, fake blood, etc)
The killer found out about it.
There are two conditions.
First, they entered the office
and took the hard drive.
Second, they knew
the curator wanted to kill them.
So they played along with his plan.
What was on the encrypted hard drive?
The encrypted hard drive
was how the killer learned
that the curator planned
to use the three corpses
to make a special drug.
They knew what the curator
was trying to do.
Only then would they take action
and try to kill him.
Right.
They had to know about it
before taking action.
(The hard drive contained evidence
of R Group's crimes)
The killer discovered
the curator's secret
and wanted to stop him.
That's why they were desperate
to kill the curator.
(The killer didn't want R Group
to abduct the trio for experiments)
There's one more thing.
My ancestor was already at my house.
He was safe.
So my motive wasn't as strong.
My motive was only to save these two.
Why did I go there that day?
First, the Thousand-Faced
Eagle King Group
asked me
to retrieve the three treasures.
I needed to save the two of them anyway,
so I came here.
That was my purpose.
(Ning Bo's defence:
He had already saved his ancestor)
(He had less motive
to save all three treasures)
(Who wanted
to save the three treasures more?)
To pull off this crime,
several conditions had to be met.
What's the first?
They knew the curator
wanted to kill them.
That's the first condition.
(Conditions for killing the curator)
Second,
they wanted to save the three treasures.
Third,
they must
have forged the mission notice.
(The killer forged
the mission notice)
I think we can rule out Ding.
He's with the thieves' group.
He couldn't belong
to two groups at once.
There'd be no reason to.
Right.
The other three
all received the same mission.
They were all tasked
with retrieving the treasures.
He wasn't in the Thousand-Faced
Eagle King group chat.
So there was no way he could know
about their plan.
(Ding Tian couldn't enter the group chat
and post the fake "mission")
(The killer could only be a member
of the Thousand-Faced Eagle King)
(Suspect list)
I have a question.
This person
must have been able
to enter the office regularly.
Who could go in and out
of the office regularly?
I think it was the cleaner.
(Yang Glory's deduction:
Ning Bo is the cleaner)
(More likely to enter
Curator Tui's office)
He has to clean it often.
He also takes out the trash.
He'd have access to all sorts of things.
That's a good point.
So whoever had the easiest access
to the office
could easily learn its layout.
The cleaner might also
have a key to the office.
What?
(He's deduction: The cleaner likely
had the curator's office key)
He's panicking.
Ning is panicking.
Go on.
You're panicking.
(Gotcha)
There's one point we overlooked.
The mission sent by
the Thousand-Faced Eagle King.
Yan Reason already said
someone had forged it.
I checked with the five core members.
They told me
they never approved this mission.
The screenshot was forged.
That means
one of the four of us
forged the notice,
claiming five admins approved it
so we could carry out the mission.
Right.
Right?
And why take a photo of him
from the front?
To stage a locked-room murder.
He went in by himself.
I'll show you the ghost soldier armor.
But don't get too close.
What do you mean?
If you get too close,
its scent will cloud your mind.
(The killer had Yan Reason take a photo)
To make it seem
(To show the victim entered alone)
that Ghost Armor
(Supporting the possession theory)
had taken control of his mind.
(Who knew
the ghost soldier legend best?)
So the killer is one of you two.
(Ning Bo's deduction: He or Jin Da)
It's that simple to me.
Of course, you could suspect us two.
You could suspect us too.
I won't say who's more suspicious.
I'll only speak for myself.
(He's defence)
We posed as ghost soldiers
to rescue the villagers.
I joined the group on May 5.
They gave me the mission on May 7.
On May 8,
heartthrob, helpful contact and I
went to the village in disguise
and rescued the villagers.
I've never been to the office.
I've never even stepped inside.
You wanted
to get your family heirloom back,
didn't you?
So you may have gone to his office
to retrieve the real painting.
Your real family heirloom.
Isn't that possible?
My family heirloom
was sold to those buyers.
I wanted to confront him.
I wanted him to buy my heirloom back
from those buyers.
When I first heard about it,
I went to his home
dressed as a ghost to scare him.
Curator Tui was terrified.
He dropped to his knees and begged,
I'll definitely
get all your things back.
He went straight
to the curator's home.
(The curator agreed
to return the treasures)
(No need to investigate
his office for now)
I believe you've all
made up your minds.
But here's what I think.
Let's use the Venn diagram again.
The overlap between the two circles
is what matters most.
That's where we're most likely
to find the killer.
The first circle
should be
the Thousand-Faced Eagle King group.
(Thousand-Faced Eagle King Group:
Jin Da, Ning Bo and He)
(The Touch Today Group: Ding)
This circle is also why
we ruled out Ding.
Right?
(Ding ruled out)
He has no ties to Eagle King.
Okay.
That's the first circle.
(Killer narrowed down
to Ning Bo, Jin Da or He)
About the second circle...
I think the most important part is...
It's the timeline.
Exactly.
They had to meet him at 10:40.
(Who had time to kill him?)
They had to prepare to strike first.
I was looking around
when someone suddenly approached me.
Hey, are you the new guard?
I said yes.
It's already ten.
What are you doing?
Hurry and join the patrol.
That worked out, so I joined them.
I rested alone
while awaiting a message
from the company.
I was repairing the treasure.
I started at ten.
I know who the killer is.
You two, stop pretending.
Alright?
(Who had the best chance
to commit the murder?)
(Can they identify the killer?)
Let's vote.
(Time to name the killer)
So many clues point to...
From every angle,
I think I'll vote for...
(Voting)
Today, he seems to be the one
everyone's targeting.
There are too many strong clues.
Every one of them
fits him perfectly.
(Voting)
So I wrote down his name.
He seems a little different today.
I wanted to save all three treasures.
He wanted to save all three too.
(Voting: He)
But Jin Da is an obvious suspect too.
She also wanted to save the treasures
(Voting)
and knew R Biotech Group's address.
So I doubt the killer would've
revealed R Biotech Group's address
under their own identity.
That means they also
posed as an Thousand-Faced
Eagle King admin
to post the mission.
I think He is
(Voting: He)
more likely to be the killer.
I voted for Ning Waver.
As a cleaner,
(Voting: Ning Waver)
he could enter the office
and uncover the information
that set everything
in motion.
Posing as a guard let him
enter the exhibition hall
and carry out his plan.
He also had plenty of time
to carry out the crime there.
And there's one more thing.
His occupation gave him an advantage.
He also had a strong motive
(Voting)
and plenty of time to do it.
If it's between those two,
(Voting)
I choose...
(Voting ends. Case archived.)
No deduction needed for travel,
save more with Tongcheng.
Now, brought to you
by Tongcheng Travel,
it's time for the truth to be revealed.
In today's case,
the suspects are
Ning Bo,
Ding Tian,
He,
and Jin Da.
After our deductions,
two suspects received votes.
(Two of the four suspects got votes)
All right.
The two suspects who received votes
are...
Ning Bo.
Oh no.
He.
(Bitter)
(Avoids eye contact)
It can't be you, can it?
(No way)
The suspect with the most votes is...
He.
Stop dragging it out.
It's me.
He.
(I knew it)
Of course.
Those who voted for He,
step forward.
Four votes. Who else could it be?
I couldn't have voted for myself.
You didn't vote for me?
I didn't.
Who did you vote for?
I voted for Ning Bo.
(Votes for Ning Bo: He and Ding Tian)
(Votes for He: Ning Bo,
Ke Stubborn, Jin Da, Yang Glory)
Do you think you voted correctly?
I don't know.
Did you identify the killer correctly,
or get it wrong?
(Is He the real killer?)
You did so well toward the end.
(So what?)
Could Ning really be the killer?
I'm gritting my teeth.
Seriously.
Those two played it so well.
They're smart.
They're really smart.
(Why does he say that?)
What do you mean?
(Ning Bo is the real killer?)
I told you.
You two, over here.
Come on.
Get ready to kneel. Come on.
Stand properly.
So who is it?
Your attempt to identify the killer...
Succeeded?
Failed.
(It isn't He)
(That leaves only...)
No way.
You were good today.
You escaped without a single vote.
I don't want to play anymore.
I don't want to film anymore.
I've never won.
(It isn't Jin Da either)
This one?
It's not me.
How could it be this one?
(That leaves you)
You got away with zero votes.
The real killer
is Jin Da.
(Failed to identify the killer)
(Pretending to be shocked)
Is it me?
Impressive.
(Much respect)
It's you.
Jin Da.
What a highlight.
A true highlight.
(Her crowning moment)
Is it really me?
(Jealous)
It's you.
(The killer)
Just look at yourselves.
Congrats, Jin Da.
You've won a golden key.
(Life's a breeze)
(The killer escaped successfully)
(Jin Da)
How did you do it?
Tell us about your big moment.
Right.
(Thursdays at noon: Dungeon Archiving)
Everything matched your deduction.
So where did I slip up?
I started working here on May 20.
(Jin Da started before all of us)
You were actually very close.
Why was I working here?
Under the guise of restoring treasures,
I secretly investigated him.
I needed to gather proof
that he was
a fake Thousand-Faced
Eagle King descendant.
One day, I snuck into his office
and took the hard drive.
When I later snuck in again,
I heard him tell his men
that I was behind it.
He wanted to kill me.
How did you get inside?
I had a staff access card.
I see.
I'd been undercover here for ages.
(Jin Da had worked there for ages)
I'd been undercover...
Right.
(Her staff card granted office access)
She'd already been working there.
I see.
That doesn't matter.
Forget it. You win.
You win.
(Not sure whether to laugh or cry)
Now we'll reveal
the key evidence you all missed.
A red thread on the victim's armor.
That thread?
(A red thread was found on the armour)
Its color
and material
were identical to the costume
Jin Da wore this morning.
Right here.
(The same material)
Before I changed clothes,
(Good catch)
I'd already spotted it.
So I stayed away.
Let's check his arm
for any marks.
Let's take a look.
Check over there.
(She saw thread matching her costume)
(So she didn't approach the evidence)
Holy moly.
Still searching?
Still want to search next time?
Everything was on my side.
All the odds favoured me.
(Humblebrag)
I almost feel bad.
How did we miss that?
(They missed the key evidence again)
You played really well.
Well played.
I never once
suspected you.
Still, you escaped without a vote.
Not one vote went to you.
(I never suspected you)
Can I ask something?
Do I get three golden keys
for escaping with zero votes?
(Seizing the chance for more keys)
Probably not. Right.
Let me tell you.
Happiness lies in contentment.
(He's motto:
Happiness lies in contentment)
All right, thank you, everyone.
What's wrong?
Quick, lock her in.
Don't lock me up.
I'm the killer. Don't lock me up.
What...
What is this?
Players,
the Door of Truth transfer system
has encountered a bug.
I'm the designer of the Door of Truth.
(Door of Truth designer: Designer Bai
Played by Bai Qichen)
Designer Bai?
I'm now granting access
for players to rate the dungeon.
Rate it?
We're rating it inside the dungeon?
(For the first two dungeon ratings,
see Dungeon Archived)
Congrats on clearing the dungeon.
Please use the scorecard
to rate this chapter of your lives.
Use the scorecard
to rate the Starlight Cafe dungeon.
It was incredible.
It's right here.
Come on.
Alright.
In this Dungeon World,
whether you were heroes or generals,
or princes and princesses of each realm,
you all wished to help the world.
You rode and fought side by side.
You kept children safe from harm
and gave the elderly peace.
Through your efforts,
the realm was safe and at peace.
Your loved ones were by your side.
Love and hate were resolved.
You lived without regret.
In future generations' eyes,
every one of you
became heroes
whose legends would live on.
Do you
like such a meaningful
and beautiful world?
This is complete nonsense.
Keep...
children safe from harm?
We only wanted to protect them.
But the children suffered a lot.
Exactly.
The elderly were displaced too.
And the realm wasn't safe
or at peace.
Right.
Exactly.
And our loved ones weren't with us.
Our friends and family all...
We all ended up homeless.
Our parents all died.
Right.
Those were the things we wanted.
No, that's how the game described it.
But what actually happened
was nothing like that.
This life story is the exact opposite
of everything I experienced.
Do you like
such a meaningful and beautiful life?
What?
Of course that's wrong.
It's completely different
from the story we lived through.
(Why is the dungeon description
so different from their experience?)
The maximum score is 100.
Let's give Designer Bai...
minus 100. How about that?
(The game doesn't match reality,
so they give it a low score)
(The game detected an anomaly.
For everyone's safety,)
(please give a high score.)
The game detected an anomaly.
For everyone's safety,
please give a high score.
Give it 100 points.
(Survival instincts maxed out)
A hundred.
Why is it threatening us?
No.
What if I refuse?
Who are you?
Zero points.
Why should I do what it says?
Though I already wrote 99.
I gave it 100.
Let me out. I want to go home.
(As expected of the detective duo)
I don't bow to pressure.
Zero points.
Bro...
We got crushed.
He's panicking.
He's lost it.
Who gave it
999 points?
Who wrote nine...
Me.
He wrote
9.9.
(How is that different from 100?)
(The game detected an anomaly.
For everyone's safety,)
(please give a high score.)
(Give it a low score!)
Someone says to score it low.
Give it a low score!
A low score? Okay.
We'll give it a low score.
(What kind of move is this?)
How did this...
I already scored it.
You gave it a high score.
Change it. Hurry.
Who gave it 99?
That was me.
There was no chivalry at all.
We...
We must stand firm.
Hurry and give it a low score.
Here.
Hurry and score it low.
Change it to a low score.
It's an obedience test.
We just do whatever we're told.
Someone is threatening us,
saying we must give a high score.
(Two opposing forces?)
Accept the threat,
(One wants high, one wants low)
and give a high score.
But if you think,
I refuse to play by their rules,
then give it a low score.
They want us to defy them.
Maybe the bad guy
wants us to score it high.
Right.
But actually,
he threatened us.
He threatened us.
Good people don't threaten others.
Right.
(Who told the players
to give a low score?)
(System error)
(System restored)
System restored.
The third game dungeon,
Ghost Stories of Tui City, is rated.
Now calculating the golden keys
earned from the third dungeon.
None.
(Dungeon 3: Zero golden keys)
Not a single one.
(Golden Key Leaderboard)
(Liu Yuning: 5. Jin Jing, Zhang Linghe,
Ding Chengxin, Zhou Keyu: 3)
(Yang Chaoyue, Wang Yuwen, Sun Qian: 1)
Golden keys.
Golden keys, here I come!
How do we open it?
We can't even open this.
No wonder I'm the dumbest one.
Could it be a drawer?
Is it this side?
Not this side.
How about
we share the key?
(Keeping the peace)
Exactly.
An anomaly was detected
in Dungeon 3.
Skill card delivery failed.
To protect the players,
you will now be transported
to Dungeon 4.
No! I haven't got my golden keys!
(Hahaha)
No!
(Opening the transport portal)
Give me my golden keys!
No!
My golden keys!
Two keys.
I have two golden keys!
Stop laughing! Help me open it!
I'm begging you!
To keep it fair,
how about none of us takes it?
No one gets it.
No, guys!
Why?
We won't take ours either.
Then nobody gains any points.
No one does.
So if you have zero,
you'll stay at zero.
And we'll still...
You'll regret this.
From this day forward,
in every dungeon to come,
I won't just kill those named Tui.
I'll kill all of you too!
Welcome aboard
the Tongcheng Travel Time Tunnel
to the dungeon world.
I'll be your guide,
Fei Ermeng from Tongcheng Travel.
Please collect your personal
dungeon passes.
Change outfits and transform.
Get ready to depart.
Investigate with ease.
I'll be with you throughout.
Let's set off with Tongcheng.
(Player Liu Yuning obtained identity:
Ning Watcha)
(Player Jin Jing obtained identity:
Jin Goofy)
(Player Zhang Linghe obtained identity:
He Struggle)
(Player Ding Chengxin obtained identity:
Ding Staring)
(Player Zhou Keyu obtained identity:
Ke Uh-Oh)
(Guest Player Zhang Ruonan identity:
Nan Shy)
(Case 4 loading...)
(After completing this story,
what are your thoughts and reflections?)
In this story,
the character I played, Hehe,
donated the treasure
from his ancestral hometown
with a very simple intention.
He hoped that this piece of history,
filled with courage
and valuable lessons,
could be seen by more people.
But someone took advantage
of that trust,
(Zuixian Inn)
turning something of public value
into a tool for personal gain.
No one should monopolize it
for their own selfish interests,
let alone profit from it.
That is a desecration of history.
I once desperately
wanted to hide away every treasure.
Later,
I finally understood
that true protection
is not about possession,
but making sure it never falls
into the hands of those
with evil intentions.
As long as there are people
willing to step forward
and protect these relics
that carry our history,
our roots will never be erased.
In this case,
much of the advanced technology
was only used for profit.
I believe we must reject
any form of illegal experimentation.
The development of technology
must never cross the boundaries of life.
As technology continues to advance,
we must always be mindful
of the red line of technological ethics.
In this case,
the tomb keeper Ning Bo
discovered that the tomb
he guarded had been robbed.
Three corpses were stolen by Curator Tui
and brought to the Tui Exhibition Hall.
(Congrats! You obtained 3 treasures.)
They were once
great heroes of their time.
Their wish was for peace
throughout the world,
but years later,
greedy descendants
turned them into tools of war.
We must uphold the boundaries
between technology and ethics,
respect life,
and never let ambition
consume our conscience.
The purpose of technological advancement
is to benefit humanity
and improve people's lives,
not to use “progress” as an excuse
to violate ordinary people's rights.
No matter how times change
or how technology evolves,
we must never sacrifice lives
for the sake of growth and progress.
Life is unique and precious,
and should never be altered recklessly.
As we gradually uncovered
the great conspiracy
behind the Tui Exhibition Hall,
I couldn't imagine
how desperate and helpless
the innocent victims must have felt.
Today's story
allows us to clearly see that
when technology loses all restraint,
the darkness of human nature
can be magnified endlessly.
The tragedy in this story
reminds us that
no technological exploration
should ever
come at the cost of human lives.
Life is never
just a cold experimental material.
Everyone's health and right to life
are inviolable boundaries.
(Hu Yingxiang, Lawyer, Law Office Wuhan)
If we conduct experiments for research,
exhibition experiences,
or public welfare projects,
without the participants' consent
and secretly carry out experiments.
It is a serious violation
of both law and ethics.
Our legal system
places the protection of people's
right to life, health,
and dignity as its highest principle.
A person's life and bodily integrity
are also the bottom line
protected by law.
No purpose,
including scientific research,
can justify infringing
upon anyone's life and health.
No one's life should ever be sacrificed,
even in the name of scientific progress.
(Case 4 Preview)
Meow.
At Tui Games Company,
the people here
take off
their human skin at night
and turn into
monsters.
(Real or unreal, strange tales)
After night falls,
severed limbs
and remains
will wander around the company.
The door is locked.
How do we get out?
Ke has disappeared too.
You...
I know you're anxious,
but calm down first.
(Human or beast, ruins everywhere)
He transformed from a human
into an animal.
Who could it be?
I can't help but start
wanting to chew on bones.
That's already a dog's behavior.
Capybara fur?
This little fox is clearly very brave.
You're going to turn into a capybara.
All his photos
have that one bunny tooth.
The rumor is actually true.
There's a hand here!
There's another foot.
There's even a human head.
The entire body has already dissolved.
(Where only the fittest survive)
This is terrifying.
The mysterious area
will appear after the bell rings.
The ritual is about to begin.
Let's punish him.
Who are we punishing?
Are we humans or animals?
We are animals.
I didn't realize it.
Capture the animals!
Let's go!
Run with me!
He locked us inside!
Get down.
Help!
This place has turned
into a building we can't escape from.
(Everything is born and destroyed,
a deceptive game of cause and effect)
(Dungeon Archive)
I am the murderer of this case, Jin Da.
(SVIP, Thurs noon. VIP, next day noon)
I joined Curator Tui's private museum
with the sole purpose
of collecting evidence of his crimes
and exposing the true face
of this hypocrite.
Since he had already designed
such an elaborate method,
then why not use his
own plan against him?
I used his scheme to kill him.
(Truth Clubhouse)
Where is this place?
(SVIP, Friday noon. VIP, next day noon)
This is my palace.
You're still living
in your princess fantasy.
Kneel down and shout,
"Long live the princess!"
Who are those people ahead?
The others?
They're tied up too, right?
Follow me.
I want to see what happens
when the lights go out tonight.
I added some
(Dungeon Unlocking)
style from European
painting art.
(SVIP, every Tuesday at noon.
VIP, next day at noon)
I think it looks extremely similar.
This is a concept
for my painting.
It's an animal,
and this is its foot.
Does such a creature really exist?
An owl?
What is this?
I can't say it's exactly the same.
Let's just say it's identical.
=The Truth (Season 4)=
(Viewing Calendar)
A brand-new investigation mini-game!
Investigation Squad is now live.
Watch and play at the same time.
Investigate alongside the players.
Immersively uncover clues
from the Door of Truth case.
Unlock chibi character skins.
Go to the Truth Season 4
on WeTV.
Tap "Play Together" below the player
and start investigating!
Go to the Truth Season 4 on WeTV.
(Case 01: Voting Now)
Tap "Play Together" below the player.
01: My Family Is a Total Mess)
Join the online hunt.
(New case every Wednesday at noon)
Become a detective.
(Results every Thursday at 6 PM)
Solve it with the detectives.
(Enter the Lock-In Challenge)
Win Golden Keys.
(Case 3 NPC Guide)
(Cui Geng, played by Cui Shaoyang)
(Corpse-carrier Servant
played by Runrun)
(Yan Reason played by Sun Leyan)
(Loser of the martial contest
played by Bu Junjie, Wei Jun’ao)
(Lord Tui played by Wang Yikun)
(Tui Subordinate played by Shen Xier)
(Ning Waver's Martial Arts Double
played by Wei Jun'ao)
(Black-Clothed Man, Killer's Double
played by Bu Junjie)
(Junzi Ruyu played by He Wenjun)
(Ritual Participants played
by Fan Daosheng, Han Xu, Yu Bo)
(Dungeon Boy played by Liu Yi)
(Caged Girl played by Bi Zixuan)
(Girl in the Box played by Meng Xinyi)
(Boatmen played by Xu Yangsheng,
Sun Pingyang)
(Guide & Black Tower Guards)
(Fu Jiahua, Yang He, Li Hebo,
Fan Daosheng, Han Xu, Yu Bo)
(Riddle Stall Owner played
by Huang Jiahui)
(Food Stall Owner played
by Dong Jiaqi Tiffany)
(Fortune Teller & Longdong Army
Former Member played by Yang Zhibo)
(Mysterious Doctor played by Lin Tan)
(Good Luck Stall Owner & Longdong Army
Former Member played by Shi Zhongyuan)
(Good Luck Doll Seller & Longdong Army
played by Meng Lingtai, Zhou Jinglin)
(Good Fortune Stall Owner & Longdong
Army played by Kong Pengrui)
(Good Fortune Stall Customer & Longdong
Army Lieutenant played by Sui Xin)
(Weapon Stall Owner played by Li Qi)
(Paper Umbrella Stall Owner played
by Yang Xinxin)
(Ironworks Stall Owner played
by Dai Daochao)
(Beast Hide Stall Owner played
by Cao Yiqiong)
(Imperial Chef Yang played by Yang Kang)
(The Two Nether Elders played
by Han Xu, Yu Bo)
(Chancellor Tui's Attendant played
by Fan Daosheng)
(Chancellor Tui played by Xu Guodong)
(Chancellor Tui's Double played
by Li Maosheng)
(Tui Huicha played by Fu Jiahua)
(Underground Coffin Soldiers played
by Dou Wengang, Chen Bangjie)
(Dungeon Ghost Soldiers played
by Du Xinyu, Bie Haolan, Liu Tianyu)
(Su Hang, Chen Jian, Bi Zixuan)
(Mass Graveyard Ghost Soldiers)
(Longdong Army)
(Curator Tui played by Shen Xier)
(Cui Boniang played by Cui Shaoyang)
(Yan Zhi played by Sun Leyan)
(Mr. He played by He Wenjun)
(An Yi played by Lin Tan)
(Tongcheng Delivery Guy played
by Meng Lingtai)
(Fake Good Samaritan or R Corporation
Leader played by Shi Zhongyuan)
(Good Samaritan played
by Sui Xin)
(Red-Clothed Henchman played
by Kong Pengrui)
(Blue-Clothed Henchman played
by Yang Zhibo)
(R Corporation Members)
(Trapped Villagers)
♪Crossing nearly a century,
fearless and undaunted♪
♪Trapped in illusions, facing setbacks,
lost in dreams♪
♪Schemes of division,
hidden plots among friends♪
♪The most intricate battles of strategy,
a silent clash of wits♪
♪The next second, deeper riddles,
or the answer to the kill♪
♪Every piece of truth
has finally come to light♪
♪Unlock the mystery, turn the question,
let's begin tonight♪
♪Side by side, no holding back,
follow every clue to find the truth♪
♪The story blurs like flowers in fog,
let's begin tonight♪
♪Search for the vanished cipher,
trace the proof, and face the sleuth♪
♪Come now, players all,
let the game of reason start♪
♪Unlock each hidden trial,
let courage spark the dark♪
♪Unravel the clues, keep searching♪
♪Find the missing codes and evidence,
piece by piece♪
♪Come now, players all,
let the game of reason start♪
♪Unlock each hidden trial,
let courage spark the dark♪
♪Unravel the clues, keep searching♪
♪Team up to expose his true colors♪